<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Example on 稻说</title>
    <link>https://minhua.netlify.app/categories/example/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Example on 稻说</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://minhua.netlify.app/categories/example/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Letter 3: On True and False Friendship</title>
      <link>https://minhua.netlify.app/post/2019/07/29/letter-3-on-true-and-false-friendship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhua.netlify.app/post/2019/07/29/letter-3-on-true-and-false-friendship/</guid>
      <description>You have sent a letter to me through the hand of a “friend” of yours, as you call him.
And in your very next sentence you warn me not to discuss with him all the matters that concern you, saying that even you yourself are not accustomed to do this; in other words, you have in the same letter affirmed and denied that he is your friend.
Now if you used this word of ours in the popular sense, and called him “friend” in the same way in which we speak of all candidates for election as “honourable gentlemen,” and as we greet all men whom we meet casually, if their names slip us for the moment, with the salutation “my dear sir,” – so be it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seneca&#39;s essays</title>
      <link>https://minhua.netlify.app/work/essays/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhua.netlify.app/work/essays/</guid>
      <description>Traditionally given in the following order:
De Providentia (On providence) - addressed to Lucilius De Constantia Sapientis (On the Firmness of the Wise Person) - addressed to Serenus De Ira (On anger) – A study on the consequences and the control of anger - addressed to his brother Novatus Ad Marciam, De consolatione (To Marcia, On Consolation) – Consoles her on the death of her son De Vita Beata (On the Happy Life) - addressed to Gallio &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seneca&#39;s tragedies</title>
      <link>https://minhua.netlify.app/work/tragedies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhua.netlify.app/work/tragedies/</guid>
      <description>Fabulae crepidatae (tragedies with Greek subjects):
Hercules or Hercules furens (The Madness of Hercules) Troades (The Trojan Women) Phoenissae (The Phoenician Women) Medea Phaedra Oedipus Agamemnon Thyestes Hercules Oetaeus (Hercules on Oeta): generally considered not written by Seneca. First rejected by Heinsius. Fabula praetexta (tragedy in Roman setting):
Octavia: almost certainly not written by Seneca (at least in its final form) since it contains accurate prophecies of both his and Nero’s deaths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letter 2: On Discursiveness in Reading</title>
      <link>https://minhua.netlify.app/post/2016/02/14/letter-2-on-discursiveness-in-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhua.netlify.app/post/2016/02/14/letter-2-on-discursiveness-in-reading/</guid>
      <description>Judging by what you write me, and by what I hear, I am forming a good opinion regarding your future.
You do not run hither and thither and distract yourself by changing your abode; for such restlessness is the sign of a disordered spirit.
The primary indication, to my thinking, of a well-ordered mind is a man’s ability to remain in one place and linger in his own company.
Be careful, however, lest this reading of many authors and books of every sort may tend to make you discursive and unsteady.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
